Seino's Galgal Channel GO!
Today we have two members of the Plastic Club!
Seino
Hello!
I'm Tako-kun!
This is Yume-chan.
I'm looking forward to meeting you.
Yay!
You're so loud!
Really? You have a tiny voice.
You've always had a quiet voice.
You have a really loud voice.
That's great.
It's not so loud.
He pulled me along nicely.
I'm sorry I said something weird.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Today's project is...
We're going to play the dance gesture game.
Have you ever played this game before?
Of course not.
I was wondering if you have.
I mean, I don't know where to look.
I was wondering if there are a lot of people on YouTube who have done it.
We only play tag.
I wanted to play tag.
You wanted to?
Next time...
Okay.
Have you ever played tag?
Yes, I've done it on the Gal Gal channel.
It's not that easy.
Let's do our best.
I'll do my best.I'll do my best.
Today we made two pairs that mixed with each other.
I would like to compete with the number of answers that my team's
I'd like to compete with you.
Yes, sir.
The team will be me and...
I'll have you call me...
Mr. Tako-kun.
To get along with each other.
Please do.
I was a little nervous about calling you by your name.
I was wondering how to call you Tako-kun, and now...
In the south.
Me and Yume
Yume-chan.
So please do me a favor.
I'd like to do it.
I'm getting nervous. You must be nervous. I'll dance with you first.
As a backup dancer, will you be okay? I'll be fine.
I'm looking forward to being a backup dancer.
I'll start with you first.
Go for it! Go for it!
I'll take care of it. I'm nervous.
How many steps are we going to do?
I don't know.
It's coming out. It's coming out fast.
I can do it.
What? That's a serious face.
I know, I know, I know!
Exterminate the demon. Exterminate the demon.
No? Nice try. Nice try.
Next! Next!
Momotaro, is that you?
Giraffe!
Sha!
Oh, this one's easy.Oh, this one's easy.
Mentante?
No, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Mentante?
Correct!
Ambulance!
What?
A police car.
What's that?
Oh, no, no, no, I got the wrong one.
Wrong?
There's no right answer.
Police!
There's no right or wrong answer.
What?
Police!
Wrong!
Aah!
Huh? Huh?
Huh?
Yes! Yes!
Why? Why?
Ninja? No.
Aah!
Aah! Aah!
What was that? Ichiro.
No, no, no, no.
It's changed. It's changed.
What should I do?
It's Mr. Goromaru.
It's changed, it's changed, it's changed.Change, change, change.
Walking the Dog
Wrong!
What's that?
He looks so happy.
Doraemon!
He's got muscles.
Sound.
It's fast.
Fast.
This project is hard
It's just my right hand.
It's just the right hand that's hard.
It's hard for me, too, when I imagine it
I can't imagine what I'm going to do next.
I wonder how many questions I got wrong
I got two wrong.
Wow, that's pretty impressive.
But I don't know how to walk a dog with that.
I got it.
You got it?
I didn't get this one.
I was a very good detective.
I was a detective up there.
What kind of super site are you practicing on?
Here we go, Mr. Taco. Good luck, Mr. Taco.
I'll do my best. I think you can tell even with your eyes closed.
I'm going with my heart. I'm going with my heart.
With confidence and vigor.
Let's start with this.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Like this, like this, like this, like this...
Okay, okay, okay.
Idol.
Yes!
Yes!Yay!
Easy to understand
Crocodile
Yes!
That's great.
That was fast.
That's good!
That's not so bad.
Oh, man.
Oh, no!
Eat big, eat big, eat big
Bear.
What?
bear
Ah-pun!
Yes!
Oh, I get it.
New song! Ping-pong! Ping-pong!
That's right!
Oh, no!
It's hard!Difficult!
Stroller! Stroller!
Stroller!
What is that?
What is it? What is it? What is it?
It's so hard!
It's floating!
Oh, my God! What's this?
It's so loud!
What's that! Oh, my God!
What, what, what, what?
Oh! Balls in the basket! Balls in the basket!
Smileys! Field day!
Yeah!
Drunk!
What? !
Wait a minute!
Isn't that awesome?
Dancer!
That's right!
I lost the subject!
I kept doing this!
Oh! Isn't that great?
Six questions!
I got one wrong!
Oh, my God!
What am I going to do! I'm not having fun and I still want to dance!
No, I didn't get it on the way!
It's definitely something like this!
This?
It's a rickshaw!
No, I don't know!
Yes, you do!
This, this, this!This, this, this!
Aah!
Did you turn your head like that?
Yes, indeed!
I was just thinking, I have to dance.
I'm moving so weirdly!
Oh, my God!
That was amazing!
I could feel it so well!
I knew it!
Yes, I got it here!
It's all about the bond!
The bond!
First day!
We're next! The biggest!
Next time, we won't be able to stand up!
We can't stand up!
You're right!
I can't stand up!
That's amazing!
I can really feel your posture.
From this side.
What kind of posture is that?
Please, leave me a scar.
Scar?
Nail marks.
Here we go.
Monkey!
That's right!
Oh, here we go.
Box.
Model!
Correct!
Great, great, great, great.Great, great, great!
Hero.
Oh, that one.
That's all we got.
The one with the flag.
SDF Garou
Finally!
He's got a big mouth!
Too big a mouth
Gungaroo.
No?
What's this?
We're the same. You guessed first.
Hamburger!
What's yours?
It's hard!
See, Piccoli's...
Right?
It's hard if you take them together.
What are you doing?
Refund party?
What?
Shipping!
What, this trampoline?
Wait, wait, wait.
Point point point point point point point point point point point point point point point point point point point point point point point point
Oh, it's me.
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
That was fast!
So fast!
Five correct answers.
That's great.
That's hard.
So 10 questions in total so far.
So that meansThis means that
If Karea gets at least 4 more questions right
We'll win.
Oh, no.
We might be in trouble.
I'll answer with my eyes closed.
Do it right.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Okay, I'll do my best next time.
Good luck.
Oh!
Nice step.
Yes, it's starting.
Yes!
What? It's starting?
I know the answer to that.
Basketball, basketball, basketball.
Basketball player.
I know what it is. I know what it is.
I don't even need to see it.
Jump rope!
That's right!
He's definitely watching.
He's doing something.
What are you doing?
Are you weak? What?
Girls Girls Girls!
No, sir!
GIRLS' GIRLS! Gal Gal Gal!
For you?
I've made up my mind!
No, no, no, not me! I'm yours!
What?
Oh!Ah!
Ah! I'm done.
That was hard!
You haven't taken any more steps.
You didn't even take the steps anymore.
What's that?
Like this?
This much?
What, what, what, what?
Hey!
I'll take care of Kaede!
That looks so hard!
No, but you should answer this one.
First grade, first grade, I'm a nerd, and Claire is a nerd.
What kind of nerd are you?
What do you do? Strength training? Bodybuilder? Claire's a bodybuilder?
What? No. Not many questions, not many questions, only about four, right?
She was talking. Was she talking?
You were talking? - No. Three?
What about Claire? Did you get three?
You lose.
I'm going to give you the box version of the question I want you to look at.
Okay, you two, answer.
I'm the best at expressing myself. I'm from Fukuoka.
I'm the best individually. Please be sure.
Table tennis.
Basketball.
This again?
I want to play this one.
Tokyo Tower. Correct.
Larry?
Drama?
How hard can it be?
Oh, I got it!
Parry Potter!Parry Potter!
Magic circle!
Correct!
Oh, no.
What kind of animal?
A rabbit?
What does it do?
But I know what it is. It's so cool.
What's this?
What is it?
What are these?
What are the other two?
Did they change the subject?
Is this the answer?
What's this?
Is that possible?
Flying?
No, sir.
[fast forward]
[laughter]
Boober and Gormon are on the case, and now they're not even related to the Downers anymore.
I hope you're right.
I don't understand this one, but this one is closer than this one.
I don't get it... but it's closer than this.
It's so cute... and then he says, "Good work.
The kamakiri is flying... and the kabakiri is flying.
It's a voluntary matter, right?
Yes, so I just finished the dance gesture...
The results... what's wrong?
I'm feeling a lot of heat.
It's a little hot.
It's incredible.
I can't stop sweating.
Cold sweat...Cold sweat and
Sweat from the kamakiri.
It's the kamakiri's fault, isn't it?
And I'm sorry I couldn't make it to the entrance ceremony.
I can't stop the praying mantis
The fish hooks won't stop...
10 points for Minami Yuna's team!
10 points
Claire, your team has 9 points
That effort was nothing.
Don't give them points for that.
That's why we won.
I see.
But we came in first individually.
Really?
Yeah.
Gold medal.
Congratulations.
How did you guys do?
Well, you know...
You know, your sense of style.
Yes, you have spirit, don't you?
After all, you answered 5 questions.
How could you answer 3 questions?
How can you answer so brazenly?
On the contrary, it was difficult.
On the contrary.
I was...
I didn't have the confidence of my imagination.
I'm glad I got three questions.
I'm glad.
I'm glad I could answer three questions, too.
Yes, I'm glad.
You can watch the video on the Pro Club's website.
Please check it out too!Please take a look at that too!
Please do.
Thank you very much.
It's a lot of fun.
Let's do it.
I don't know how it ended.
You were done with the go-go.
No, it didn't.
That's not true.
I'm wearing D-Holic's costume this time.